thedarkgames.com 2012-06-22

# Privacy Policy - Dark Games

Privacy Policy

Dark Games is committed to providing an entertaining, fun and educational service. Dark Games respects the privacy concerns of its visitors. Dark Games does not target its website or services to under 13 year olds, but does take measures to help protect those that happen to be under 13. We take measures to help children protect their privacy while online. For example, we do not ask children to disclose more personal information than is necessary for them to participate in a particular activity. 

### Information we collect

When you visit our website we collect some information from you. We collect no personally identifiable information such as your name, address, phone number, or e-mail address unless you willingly submit it to us via registration or contact. Some types of non-personally identifiable information such as the Internet Service Provider you use to connect to the internet, your browser type, or the type of computer operating system you use is collected upon your visit to our site in order to provide our advertisers with targeting information. 

### How we use the information

We have an internal system to communicate and track visitors to correct our own stats and we do not send them any emails. We do not retain any personal information beyond the time it is needed. We may use information to ensure that users are compliance with our terms. We may sometimes use non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our site, to personalize our visitors' experience or to offer products, programs, and services. We may also use this information in the aggregate to analyze site usage, as well as to offer products, programs, or services. 

### Security

We have implemented appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the information we collect online. 

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy which you agree to by accessing the Dark Games.com website and/or services. You agree that Dark Games may change this Privacy Policy at any time. Our current Privacy Policy will be posted here and visitors may contact us using the contact page. 

### Internet Safety

Dark Games recommends that Parents take time to communicate and educate their children about Internet Safety. Please see the Internet Safety webpage for information on Internet Safety: <http://www.kidsmart.org.uk/>

More Information regarding the privacy policy please check out this site: <http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html>
